Guide to the Yale University Library Name/Title Card Catalog
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Yale University Library name/title card catalog
1860-1979
RU 1120
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
4453.5
(8907 boxes)
Yale University. Library
Scope and Contents
The materials consist of the Yale University Library name/title catalog cards, which were retrospectively converted to electronic format.
Existence and Location of Copies
The entire name/title catalog is available via ORBIS, the Yale University Library online public access catalog (OPAC).
Related Materials
Related materials: Yale University Library Subject Card Catalog (RU 982).
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Transferred from the Yale University Library, 2012.
General
Forms part of Yale Record Group 32-C (YRG 32-C), Records of Yale University Library departments and offices.
Arrangement
The materials are arranged alphabetically by name and title.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Library catalogs; Yale University. Library -- Catalogs
- Symbols (Box 1)
- Numbers (Titles) 1860 (Box 2)
- A.A. (Box 3)
- A.C.L.O. (Box 4)
- A.F.S.A.A.P. (Box 5)
- A.L.I.D.E. (Box 6)
- A.P.R.A. (Box 7)
- A.S.R. (Box 8)
- Abo-akademi (continued) (Box 9)
- Aarhus (Box 10)
- Abadim (Box 11)
- Abbassah (Box 12)
- Abbot (Box 13)
- Abbott, Jacob (continued) (Box 14)
- Abd-al-Aziz (Box 15)
- Abd-al Maqsud (Box 16)
- Abd-al-Wahid (continued) (Box 17)
- Abdeslam Sefiri (Box 18)
- Abdullah (Box 19)
- A Becket (Box 20)
- Abelard (Box 21)
- Aber-Adolf (Box 22)
- Abes (Box 23)
- Abhandlungen (continued) (Box 24)
- Abhinanda (Box 25)
- Abner, Liebet (Box 26)
- Aboting (Box 27)
- Abraham (continued) (Box 28)
- Abrahams, P. (Box 29)
- Abramson, Adolph G. (Box 30)
- Abro, A. (Box 31)
- Abstracts of health care (Box 32)
- Abu al-Qasim (Box 33)
- Abu Ras, al Shafi'i (Box 34)
- Abuse (Box 35)
- Academia de (Box 36)
- Academia National de la Historia (Venezuela) (Box 37)
- Academia salvadorena (Box 38)
- Academie des sciences (Box 39)
- Academie royale (Box 40)
- Academie des sciences...Brussels (continued) (Box 41)
- Acadian odyssey (Box 42)
- Accademia di belle arti (Box 43)
- Accademia Senese (Box 44)
- Acconci (Box 45)
- Accountability (Box 46)
- Acevedo (Box 47)
- Achet pya (Box 48)
- Acidini, C. (Box 49)
- Acland (Box 50)
- Acque (Box 51)
- Acta Asiatica (Box 52)
- Acta palaentologica (Box 53)
- Acta Universitatis Stockholm (Box 54)
- Acta zoologica (Box 55)
- Active (Box 56)
- Acuna (Box 57)
- Adair, A. (Box 58)
- Adam, K. (Box 59)
- Adamic, Louis (Box 60)
- Adams, Charles Francis (Box 61)
- Adams, George Irving (Box 62)
- Adams, John (Box 63)
- Adams, M. (Box 64)
- Adams, T. (Box 65)
- Adamson, P. (Box 66)
- Addington (Box 67)
- Addition (Box 68)
- Address to the six nations (Box 69)
- Adelos (Box 70)
- Adhemar (Box 71)
- Adkin (Box 72)
- Adler, N. (Box 73)
- Administrative feedback (Box 74)
- Adolph, Hans J. (Box 75)
- Adri (Box 76)
- Advanced concepts in physical... (Box 77)
- Advances in experiential s... (Box 78)
- Adventurer (Box 79)
- Advertising (Box 80)
- Aebischer, Max (Box 81)
- Aeneas (Box 82)
- Aeschylus (continued) (Box 83)
- Aesopus (translations) (continued) (Box 84)
- Afanasii, Abp. (Box 85)
- Afghanistan (Box 86)
- Africa in struggle (Box 87)
- African collection (Box 88)
- African observer (Box 89)
- African Writers Association (Box 90)
- Afrikanische (Box 91)
- After (Box 92)
- Against perspective (Box 93)
- Agate (Box 94)
- Aged Poor in England and Wales (Box 95)
- Agge, Ivar (Box 96)
- Agnew (Box 97)
- Agra Europe (Box 98)
- Agresti, Domenico di (Box 99)
- Agricultural innovations in Indian villages (Box 100)
- Agrippa von Nettesheim (Box 101)
- Aguilar (Box 102)
- Aguirre Vasconez, Francisco Esteban (Box 103)
- Ahi Esta (Box 104)
- Ahmad Kamruddin (Box 105)
- Ahmad M. Hoesni (Box 106)
- Ahora viene lo mejor (Box 107)
- Ai hsin ti fu yang (Box 108)
- Aides et measures de sauvegarde en... (Box 109)
- Aikin, L. (Box 110)
- Ainsworth Family (Box 111)
- Aircraft (titles, phrases, etc.) (Box 112)
- Aitken, W. (Box 113)
- Ajhizat tanzim ai-mujtama (Box 114)
- Ajia no masu komyunikeshon (Box 115)
- Akademie der Wissenschaften (Box 116)
- Akademie der Wissenschaften. Goettingen. Philologisch-historische Klasse. Abhandlungen...N.F. Bd.15... (Box 117)
- Akademiia na naukitie (Box 118)
- Akademiia nauk SSSR. Arkheograficheskaia komissiia. Leningradskoe (Box 119)
- Akademiia nauk SSSR. Institut khimicheskoi (Box 120)
- Akademiia nauk SSSR. Marine (Box 121)
- Akademiia nauk SSSR (subject) (Box 122)
- Akademiia obschestvennykh nauk (Moscow, R.S.R.S.R.) K. (Box 123)
- Akatdamkoeng Raphiphat (Box 124)
- Akhmatova, Anna Andreevna (Box 125)
- Akita-shi Kyoiku Iinkai (Box 126)
- Akshinskii, V.S. (Box 127)
- Akul'shin (Box 128)
- Al-Yassini Ayman (Box 129)
- Alabama museum (Box 130)
- Alamo (Box 131)
- Alaska (author) (Box 132)
- Alaux (Box 133)
- Albany N.Y. Chamber of comm. (Box 134)
- Albeg, Eduard (Box 135)
- Albert (surname) (Box 136)
- Alberta, University, Edmonton (Box 137)
- Albertinus (Box 138)
- Albin (Box 139)
- Albrecht (surname) (Box 140)
- Album (Box 141)
- Alcan (Box 142)
- Alcoholic and the group (Box 143)
- Alderoft, Derek (Box 144)
- Aldington (Box 145)
- Aldrich, Virgil Charles (Box 146)
- Alejo, Ana Elena (Box 147)
- Alekseev, S. (Box 148)
- Alencastre, Alvaro (Box 149)
- Alexander (the Great) (Box 150)
- Alexander, C. (Box 151)
- Alexander, Joseph (Box 152)
- Alexander, H. Rivell (Box 153)
- Alexandrian, Sarane (Box 154)
- Alfassa (Box 155)
- Alford (Box 156)
- Alge (Box 157)
- Algerien (Box 158)
- Ali, H. (Box 159)
- Ali Khan (Box 160)
- Alier, Juan Martinez (Box 161)
- Alison (Box 162)
- All hands (Box 163)
- Alla (Box 164)
- Allard (Box 165)
- Allegri (Box 166)
- Allen, D. (Box 167)
- Allen, H. (Box 168)
- Allen, L. (Box 169)
- Allen, Thomas (Box 170)
- Allendorf (Box 171)
- Allgemeine Geschichte (Box 172)
- Allied and associated powers (Greece) (Box 173)
- Allis (Box 174)
- Alloyd Electronics (Box 175)
- Almagor, D. (Box 176)
- Almanaque (Box 177)
- Almengor, L. (Box 178)
- Alone (Box 179)
- Alpagot (Box 180)
- Alphonse (Box 181)
- Alston (Box 182)
- Altcechische K. (Box 183)
- Altercatio (Box 184)
- Althans, G. (Box 185)
- Altmann (Box 186)
- Al'tshuler, A. (Box 187)
- Alvarado, S. (Box 188)
- Alvarez Espino (Box 189)
- Alvesson (Box 190)
- Amachua (Box 191)
- Amalteo (Box 192)
- Amarasimba (Box 193)
- Amb la mort... (Box 194)
- Ambrosius, S. (continued) (Box 195)
- Amelung (Box 196)
- America la bien (Box 197)
- American Academy of Family (Box 198)
- American Academy of Political and Social Science, Philadelphia (Box 199)
- American anti-slavery (Box 200)
- American Association for Labor Legislation (Box 201)
- American Association of (Box 202)
- American Association of University Women(continued) (Box 203)
- American Bar Association Section (continued) (Box 204)
- American bookmaker (Box 205)
- American Chemical Society (continued) (Box 206)
- American Chemical Society. Division of Polymeric (Box 207)
- American College of Surgeons (Box 208)
- American Council of Learned Societies (continued) (Box 209)
- American Country Life Conference (Box 210)
- American education (Box 211)
- American Enterprise Institute for Public Policy Research (continued) (Box 212)
- American Federation of Austrian Democrats (Box 213)
- American Free trade League (Box 214)
- American geopolitics and India (Box 215)
- American Historical Association. Immigration(continued) (Box 216)
- American Indian Institute (Box 217)
- American Institute of Certified Public Accountants (continued) (Box 218)
- American Institute of Physics (continued) (Box 219)
- American journal of hygiene (Box 220)
- American law institute (Box 221)
- American Library Association, Division of Cataloging and Classification (Box 222)
- American management association (continued) (Box 223)
- American Mental Health Foundation (Box 224)
- American Nation (Box 225)
- American Oriental Society (Box 226)
- American Philosophical Society (continued) (Box 227)
- American politics (Box 228)
- American Public Welfare Association (Box 229)
- American-Scandinavian Foundation, N.Y. (Box 230)
- American Social Science Association (Box 231)
- American Society of Anesthesiologists (Box 232)
- American Society of Railroad S. (Box 233)
- American studies monograph series (Box 234)
- American Transit Association (Box 235)
- American University of Beirut (Box 236)
- American writers and the great depression (Box 237)
- America's spiritual recovery (Box 238)
- Amersham, English. Radiochemical Centre (Box 239)
- Amherst (titles, etc.) (Box 240)
- Amiel, J. (Box 241)
- Amir, M. (Box 242)
- Ammen (Box 243)
- Among ancient ruins (Box 244)
- Amos, S. (Box 245)
- Amr ibn Ubayd (Box 246)
- Amsterdam (titles, etc.) (Box 247)
- Amyot, M. (Box 248)
- Anacreon (Box 249)
- Analecta Vaticano-Belgica (Box 250)
- Analpha (Box 251)
- Analysis of the resource (Box 252)
- Anan'ev, Boris G. (Box 253)
- Anatomy (titles, etc.) (Box 254)
- Anchieta, J. (Box 255)
- Ancient Ireland (Box 256)
- ...And then I told the President (Box 257)
- Anderson, Arne S. (Box 258)
- Anderson, Alexander (Box 259)
- Anderson, Eugene D. (Box 260)
- Anderson, John Ansel (Box 261)
- Anderson, Paul Sigfried (Box 262)
- Anderson, Walter (Box 263)
- Andesu (Box 264)
- Andra historiska facta (Box 265)
- Andre (Box 266)
- Andreas, Adam (Box 267)
- Andren, Greta (Box 268)
- Andrews (Box 269)
- Andrews, John Bertram (Box 270)
- Andreev, Leonid Nikolaevich (continued) (Box 271)
- Androsky, Albert (Box 272)
- Anesthesia (medical) (Box 273)
- Angeli, Moriz E. (Box 274)
- Angelov, Dimitar (Box 275)
- Angkor, Cambodia (Box 276)
- Anglistische studien (Box 277)
- Anglo-Saxon church (Box 278)
- Angulos (Box 279)
- Animal cognition (Box 280)
- Anjou (Box 281)
- Annadurai, C.N. (Box 282)
- Annales Hiberniae (Box 283)
- Annals of pioneer settlers (Box 284)
- Annee (Box 285)
- Annotated Bankers (Box 286)
- Annuaire hydrologique de la Republique populaire du Congo (Box 287)
- Annual report of dialectology (Box 288)
- Anonimo lambardo (Box 289)
- Ansari, F. (Box 290)
- Ansichten und Umrisse (Box 291)
- Answer to P. (Box 292)
- Anterem (Box 293)
- Anthon (Box 294)
- Anthropological religion (Box 295)
- Anti-Catalog (Box 296)
- Anti-Jacobin (Box 297)
- Antipode (Box 298)
- Anti-Slavery Society of New York City (Box 299)
- Antologia de la tierra (Box 300)
- Anton, Francisco (Box 301)
- Antonio Conselheiro (Box 302)
- Antropos (Box 303)
- Anuario eclesiastico (Box 304)
- Anwar, S. (Box 305)
- Aoki, Kisaku, 1917- (Box 306)
- Apartheid pro en contra (Box 307)
- Apidologie (Box 308)
- Apollon dans Pindares (Box 309)
- Apor, Peter (Box 310)
- Appalachian Kentucky (Box 311)
- Appell, Herbert R. (Box 312)
- Appleton, Lewis (Box 313)
- Applied optics (Box 314)
- Approaching general election (Box 315)
- Apthorp (Box 316)
- Aqqad, Abbas Mahmud, 1889-1964 (continued) (Box 317)
- Arab executive (Box 318)
- Arabica; revue... (Box 319)
- Arai, Hajime, 1933- (Box 320)
- Arana de Love, Francisca (Box 321)
- Aratus, Solensis (Box 322)
- Arbeiten (continued) (Box 323)
- Arbeitsgemeinschaft fur Freie Menschenbildung (Box 324)
- Arbes (Box 325)
- Arc (Box 326)
- Archaeological/Anthropological Association (Box 327)
- Archaeologische Kama-Expedition, 1929-27 (Box 328)
- Archeion (Box 329)
- Archibald (Box 330)
- Architectural monograph (Box 331)
- Archiv fur (Box 332)
- Archives and the Computer (Box 333)
- Archives des (Box 334)
- Archives of psychology (Box 335)
- Archivio Vaticano (Box 336)
- Archiwa (Box 337)
- Ardabili (Box 338)
- Area, Leandro (Box 339)
- Arendt (Box 340)
- Arewa, Ojo (Box 341)
- Argentina. Banco (Box 342)
- Argentina. Economia (Box 343)
- Argentina. U.C.R. (Box 344)
- Arguelles, I. (Box 345)
- Arhiv bioloskih (Box 346)
- Ariens (Box 347)
- Ariosto, Lodovico (continued) (P) (Box 348)
- Aristophanes (author) (Box 349)
- Aristotle (Box 350)
- Aristotle. Meteorologica (Box 351)
- Aristotle. Politeia (Box 352)
- Aristotle (subject) (L) (Box 353)
- Aristov, G.V. (Box 354)
- Arizona Republic (Box 355)
- Arkansas law review (Box 356)
- Arkhiyon ha-tsiyoni (Box 357)
- Arlt, Carl, 1866- (Box 358)
- Armed Forces of South Africa (Box 359)
- Arminan, L. (Box 360)
- Arms Control Association (Box 361)
- Armstrong, M. (continued) (Box 362)
- Arnaldus (Box 363)
- Arndt (Box 364)
- Arnheim, R. (Box 365)
- Arnold, D. (Box 366)
- Arnold, Matthew (continued) (Box 367)
- Arnold, William J. (Box 368)
- Arnup, J. (Box 369)
- Around the Black Sea (Box 370)
- Arragon, G. (Box 371)
- Arrington, L. (Box 372)
- Ars rhetorica (Box 373)
- Art and morals (Box 374)
- Art H (Box 375)
- Art of F. Scott Fitzgerald (Box 376)
- Art talk (Box 377)
- Arte moderna italiana (Box 378)
- Arthur, King (Box 379)
- Arthur Dove (Box 380)
- Artigas (Box 381)
- Artman (Box 382)
- Arts et lettres (Box 383)
- Arundel Society (Box 384)
- As (Box 385)
- Asahi Shimbun (Tokyo) (Box 386)
- Asaria, Zvi (Box 387)
- Ascham (Box 388)
- Asensio (Box 389)
- Ashby (Box 390)
- Ashikaga (Box 391)
- Ashmolean Museum (Box 392)
- Ashwell (Box 393)
- Asian Beacon (vol. 1) (Box 394)
- Asiatic Society (Box 395)
- Askew (Box 396)
- Asociacion de Escritores Venezolanes (Box 397)
- Asoka Rudra (Box 398)
- Aspects inductive logic (Box 399)
- Aspetti di (Box 400)
- Assassination (Box 401)
- Assiento (Box 402)
- Associated Press (Box 403)
- Association for Asian Studies (continued) (Box 404)
- Association Francaise (Box 405)
- Association of American railroads (continued) (Box 406)
- Association of Medical... (Box 407)
- Association Phonetique (Box 408)
- Ast (Box 409)
- Astralagus (Box 410)
- Asturias (Box 411)
- At the dawning (Box 412)
- Atchison (Box 413)
- Athanasius (Box 414)
- Athens, Ga. (Box 415)
- Atitlayapan (Box 416)
- Atlantic (Box 417)
- Atkinson, F. (Box 418)
- Atlantis (Box 419)
- Atlas mira (Box 420)
- Atlas Universel (Box 421)
- Atri (Italy) (Box 422)
- Atterbury, G. (Box 423)
- Attleboro, Mass. (Box 424)
- Au gaz naturel (Box 425)
- Aubin (Box 426)
- Auckland (Box 427)
- Audibert (Box 428)
- Aue (Box 429)
- Aufderbeck, H. (Box 430)
- Augier (Box 431)
- Auguste (Box 432)
- Augustinus, A. (Box 433)
- Augustinus, A (continued) (Box 434)
- Auk (Box 435)
- Aunis (Box 436)
- Aurore (Box 437)
- Aus der (Box 438)
- Aust (Box 439)
- Austin, F. (Box 440)
- Australia (Box 441)
- Australia. D (continued) (Box 442)
- Australia. P (continued) (Box 443)
- Australian (continued) (Box 444)
- Australian H (Box 445)
- Australian new (Box 446)
- Austria. Direction (Box 447)
- Austro-Hungarian Monarchy. M (Box 448)
- Authority to C. (Box 449)
- Automatic control t. (Box 450)
- Autoroute (Box 451)
- Ava (Box 452)
- Avebury (Box 453)
- Aventures sur (Box 454)
- Avery Library (Box 455)
- Avicenna f. (Box 456)
- Avne Y. (Box 457)
- Awad, R. (Box 458)
- Axelrad (Box 459)
- Ayars (Box 460)
- Ayloffe (Box 461)
- Aysma, J. (Box 462)
- Azarbaijan (continued) (Box 463)
- Azhenov, M. (Box 464)
- Azuero, A. (Box 465)
- B., J. (Box 466)
- B.A.R. international (continued) (Box 467)
- Ba, B. (Box 468)
- Baba, A. (Box 469)
- Babcock family (Box 470)
- Babkin (Box 471)
- Bacchi (Box 472)
- Bacha (Box 473)
- Bachmann, C.L. (Box 474)
- Backer, H. (Box 475)
- Bacon (Box 476)
- Bacon, F. (continued) (Box 477)
- Bacon, V. (Box 478)
- Badaro, A. (Box 479)
- Baden-R. (Box 480)
- Badischer, L. (Box 481)
- Baedeker, K. (Box 482)
- Baerie (Box 483)
- Baffo (Box 484)
- Baghdady (Box 485)
- Bagulay (Box 486)
- Bahi, S. (Box 487)
- Baid (Box 488)
- Bailey, El. (Box 489)
- Bailey, R. (Box 490)
- Baillie, G. (Box 491)
- Baines, F. (Box 492)
- Baishev, S. (Box 493)
- Bakat (Box 494)
- Baker, G. (Box 495)
- Baker, N. (Box 496)
- Bakewell (Box 497)
- Bakro (Box 498)
- Balachov (Box 499)
- Balanus (Box 500)
- Balcer (Box 501)
- Baldick (Box 502)
- Baldwin, H. (Box 503)
- Bale (Box 504)
- Bali, P. (Box 505)
- Bali, John (Box 506)
- Ballads, poems, lyrics (Box 507)
- Ballem (Box 508)
- Ballot (author) (Box 509)
- Balsamo (Box 510)
- Baltimore. N. (Box 511)
- Baluze (Box 512)
- Balzac, H. (Box 513)
- Bambynek, W. (Box 514)
- Banca del d. (Box 515)
- Banco Central P. (continued) (Box 516)
- Banco Nacional de A. (Box 517)
- Band r. (Box 518)
- Bandoeng (Box 519)
- Bang, I. (Box 520)
- Bangs, John Kendrick (continued) (Box 521)
- Bank Negara Indonesia (Box 522)
- Bank R. (Box 523)
- Banks, John R. (Box 524)
- Bannister (Box 525)
- Banten, I. (Box 526)
- Baptist missionary review (Box 527)
- Bar-Hillel, Yeoshua (Box 528)
- Barakah, A. (Box 529)
- Barath, Eugen (Box 530)
- Barbaro, Federico (Box 531)
- Barber, John Warner (Box 532)
- Barbi, Silvana (Box 533)
- Barbosa, Rolmes (Box 534)
- Barcelona. Consell de cent jurats (Box 535)
- Barclay family (Box 536)
- Bardon, Jack I. (Box 537)
- Bargain, Michel (Box 538)
- Baring, Maurice (Box 539)
- Barker, Ernest, Sir (Box 540)
- Barkhudarov, S.G. (Box 541)
- Barlow, Joel (continued) (Box 542)
- Barnard, J. (Box 543)
- Barnes, F. (Box 544)
- Barnes family (Box 545)
- Barney, Keith Richard (Box 546)
- Baroja, Pio (Box 547)
- Baroque lyric (Box 548)
- Barragan, J.L. (Box 549)
- Barreneche, Juan A. (Box 550)
- Barrett, David (Box 551)
- Barrie, Sir James Matthew (continued) (Box 552)
- Barrie, Sir James Matthew (subject) (Box 553)
- Barrios Sosa, C. (Box 554)
- Barrow, David (Box 555)
- Barry, Kathleen (Box 556)
- Bartels (Box 557)
- Barth, K. (Box 558)
- Barton, J. (Box 559)
- Bartsch, I. (Box 560)
- Barye, A. (Box 561)
- Bascom, J. (Box 562)
- Bashkirskie n (Box 563)
- Basic t. (Box 564)
- Basing point (Box 565)
- Basler Studien (Box 566)
- Basse (Box 567)
- Bast (Box 568)
- Bastos, Leonidas Castro (Box 569)
- Batalha Naval (Box 570)
- Bateman, Thomas (Box 571)
- Bates, Neil (Box 572)
- Batilliat, Rene (Box 573)
- Battaille (Box 574)
- Battle, R. (Box 575)
- Bau (Box 576)
- Baudelaire, C. (continued) (Box 577)
- Baudry, M. (Box 578)
- Bauer, P. (Box 579)
- Bauke (Box 580)
- Bauman, Richard (Box 581)
- Baumgarten (Box 582)
- Baur, Ferdinand Christian (Box 583)
- Bavaria (Germany) (Box 584)
- Baxter, James Phinney (Box 585)
- Bayanese marriage (Box 586)
- Bayerische Akad. d. Wissenschaften (continued) (Box 587)
- Bayerova, Marie (Box 588)
- Baylor, George, b. 1843 (Box 589)
- Bays (Box 590)
- Bazin, Rene (Box 591)
- Beacon (Box 592)
- Beals, Frank Lee, 1881- (Box 593)
- Beard, G. (Box 594)
- Beasley, R. Scott (Box 595)
- Beatty, P. (Box 596)
- Beaujeu, Jacques Delaurens de (Box 597)
- Beaumont, G. (Box 598)
- Beautiful Theories (Box 599)
- Bebbington, Gillian (Box 600)
- Becher, J (Box 601)
- Beck, F. (Box 602)
- Beck, Franz Arnold von der (Box 603)
- Becker, J (Box 604)
- Beckett, Francis, 1868- (Box 605)
- Beckh (Box 606)
- Becman, Friedrich (Box 607)
- Bedel, Agnes Allroggen (Box 608)
- Bedlow, Henry, 1821-1914 (Box 609)
- Beecher (Box 610)
- Beekman, W. (Box 611)
- Beerbohm, Max, 1872- (Box 612)
- Beethoven, Ludwig van, 1770-1827 (subject) (Box 613)
- Begbie (Box 614)
- Begriff Hellenismusals Epochenname (Box 615)
- Behavioral Approach (Box 616)
- Behne (Box 617)
- Behrs (Box 618)
- Beilin, Zehava (Box 619)
- Beitraege und Berichte (Box 620)
- Beitraege zur Geologie (Box 621)
- Beitraege zur Kirchengeschichte (Box 622)
- Beitraege zur russichen (Box 623)
- Bek (Box 624)
- Belanteur, Saïd (Box 625)
- Beleno, Joaquin, 1922- (Box 626)
- Belgium. Bankcommissie (Box 627)
- Belgium. Service Geologique (Box 628)
- Beliakov, Boris Nikolaevich (Box 629)
- Belknap (Box 630)
- Bell, Dennis R. (Box 631)
- Bell, M. (Box 632)
- Bell Telephone Laboratories, Inc. (Box 633)
- Bellasis, Margaret (Box 634)
- Belli (Box 635)
- Bello (Box 636)
- Bellotti, Felice (Box 637)
- Belohlavek, John M. (Box 638)
- Belt (Box 639)
- Bem (Box 640)
- Ben-Dor, Gabriel (Box 641)
- Benac, Henri, 1913- (Box 642)
- Benda, Jaroslav, 1882- (Box 643)
- Bendz, Gerd (Box 644)
- Benedict, G. (Box 645)
- Beneke, G. (Box 646)
- Benet Goitia, Juan (Box 647)
- Benhabib, Seyla (Box 648)
- Benjamin, Iramaya (Box 649)
- Benn (Box 650)
- Bennett, C. (Box 651)
- Bennett, K.F. (Box 652)
- Beno, Jan (Box 653)
- Benski, Morduch (Box 654)
- Benson, S. (Box 655)
- Bentinck Family (Box 656)
- Benton, J. (Box 657)
- Benz, Eva-Maria Hanebutt (Box 658)
- Beraettaren i Mangskog (Box 659)
- Berck (Box 660)
- Berendes (Box 661)
- Berezin, M.A. (Box 662)
- Berg, W. (Box 663)
- Bergenfeldt, Ernst Magnus, 1890- (Box 664)
- Berger, M. (Box 665)
- Bergh (Box 666)
- Bergman, Ingmar, 1918- (Box 667)
- Bergson, Henri, 1859-1941 (Box 668)
- Berichte ueber Landwirtschaft (Box 669)
- Berkeley, George, 1685-1753 (Individual works) (continued) (Box 670)
- Berkner (Box 671)
- Berlin, Brent (Box 672)
- Berlin. Deutsches Institut (Box 673)
- Berlin. Vaterlaendischer Schriften-Verband (Box 674)
- Berliner Landseen (Box 675)
- Berman, M. (Box 676)
- Bernal, J. (Box 677)
- Bernard, C. (Box 678)
- Bernard, T. (Box 679)
- Bernasconi (Box 680)
- Bernett, Hajo (Box 681)
- Bernice P. Bishop estate (Box 682)
- Bernstein (Box 683)
- Beroaldus, Matthaeus (Box 684)
- Berry, C. (Box 685)
- Berschin, Helmut, 1940- (Box 686)
- Berthelot (Box 687)
- Bertine, Kathe K (Box 688)
- Bertram, J. (Box 689)
- Berul, Lawrence (Box 690)
- Beschi (Box 691)
- Bess (Box 692)
- Best, H. (Box 693)
- Besters, Hans (Box 694)
- Betancur, Belisario, 1923- (Box 695)
- Bethune (surname) (Box 696)
- Betten (Box 697)
- Betuleius, Xystus (Box 698)
- Beurdeley, C. (Box 699)
- Beveridge, W. (Box 700)
- Bewick (Box 701)
- Beyerl, Jan (Box 702)
- Beyond Venus (Box 703)
- Bezou (Box 704)
- Bhagwatwar, P.A. (Box 705)
- Bhatia, Tej K. (Box 706)
- Bhu-vidya (Box 707)
- Bianchi (Box 708)
- Bibeau, Don (Box 709)
- Bible. Chinese (Box 710)
- Bible. English (texts) Anchor Bible (Box 711)
- Bible. English (texts) Revised, American (Box 712)
- Bible. English. New Testament. Acts (continued) (Box 713)
- Bible. English. Old Testament. Paraphrases (Box 714)
- Bible. English. Old Testament. Minor Prophets (Box 715)
- Bible. English (Basic English) (Box 716)
- Bible. German. New Testament (Box 717)
- Bible. Greek. New Testament (by editor and translator) Estienne (Box 718)
- Bible. Greek. Old Testament. Apocrypha (continued) (Box 719)
- Bible. Hebrew. Old Testament. Isaiah (Box 720)
- Bible. Kafir (Box 721)
- Bible. Latin. Old Testament. Psalms (Box 722)
- Bible. Swedish (Box 723)
- Bible-Biography (Box 724)
- Bible-Dictionaries and Encyclopedias (continued) (Box 725)
- Bible-Manuscripts (Box 726)
- Bible. New Testament (subject) (Box 727)
- Bible. New Testament. Acts (Box 728)
- Bible. New Testament. Gospels (P) (Box 729)
- Bible. New Testament. Matthew (by chapters) (Box 730)
- Bible. Old Testament-Concordances (Box 731)
- Bible. Old Testament-Ladino-Versions (Box 732)
- Bible. Old Testament. Exodus (Box 733)
- Bible. Old Testament. Jeremiah (Box 734)
- Bible. Old Testament. Pentateuch. Coptic (Box 735)
- Bible. Old Testament. Psalms (Box 736)
- Bible in Israeli Education (Box 737)
- Bibliografia Baiana (Box 738)
- Bibliografia Scalonych (Box 739)
- Bibliographia (Box 740)
- Bibliographical Society of Canada (Box 741)
- Bibliographie (Box 742)
- Bibliographische (Box 743)
- Bibliography (K) (Box 744)
- Bibliography of Water C. (Box 745)
- Biblioteca Americana (Box 746)
- Biblioteca Clasica (Box 747)
- Biblioteca de Mayo (Box 748)
- Biblioteca di studi Americani (Box 749)
- Biblioteca Nacional de Honduras (Box 750)
- Biblioteca SAC (Box 751)
- Biblioteka "Legende" (Box 752)
- Biblioteka Walczacej Polski, London. (Box 753)
- Bibliotheca I. (Box 754)
- Bibliothek der Kirchenvaeter (40 B.D.) (Box 755)
- Bibliotheque de l'enseignement de l'histoire Ecclesiastique (Box 756)
- Bibliotheque du Voyage... (Box 757)
- Bibliotheque Scientifique (Box 758)
- Bickermann, Hans Gerhard (Box 759)
- Biddle, J. (Box 760)
- Bieda, Ken (Box 761)
- Bieloblotskii, Sergei (Box 762)
- Bierce, Ambrose (Box 763)
- Big (Box 764)
- Bigelow, Karl W. (Karl Worth) (Box 765)
- Bigourdan (Box 766)
- Biko Inquest (Box 767)
- Bildung, Gesellschaft, Politik (Box 768)
- Billard (Box 769)